gftuk.com 2015-06-21

# 

Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to us, and maintaining your trust and confidence is one of our highest priorities. We respect your right to
keep your personal information confidential and we understand your desire to avoid unwanted solicitations. We hope that by taking
a few minutes to read our Privacy Policy, you will have a better understanding of what we do with the information you provide us and
how we keep it private and secure.
What types of information does GFT Markets collect?
We may collect both personal information and aggregate visitor information from our customers and visitors to our websites.
The term "personal information" means information that can identify an individual or be identified back to an individual. Personal
information collected may include data such as:
•      Contact information (name, address, phone number, email)
•      Government issued ids and employment information
•      Account balances and transaction history
•      Credit history and investment experience
The term "aggregate visitor information" is a compilation of information that does not identify an individual, such as:
•      Date and time of visit
•      IP addresses
•      Demographic information
•      Website pages visited
•      Browser used
How does GFT Markets collect my personal information?
We generally obtain personal information directly from you through applications and other forms. We may also obtain personal
information from other sources including your transactions with us, our affiliates, or others.
What does GFT Markets do with my personal information?
GFT Markets considers your information to be a vital part of our relationship with you. If you provide us with your personal
information, we will only use your personal information in ways that are consistent with the reason for which it was provided. We will
not use your personal information for any other purpose without your consent. However, if you choose not to provide us with your
personal information or wish to withdraw your consent for continued use of your personal information, we may not be able to provide
you with the services you requested.
How we may use your Personal Information                                                     Can you limit        Consent
                                                                                             this usage?
For our everyday business purposes – Such as to open and maintain your account,              No                   Implicit
process your requests and transactions, provide customer service, and comply with
legal obligations.
For our direct marketing purposes – To inform you about our products and services            Yes                  Explicit
that may be of interest to you (please see below to limit the ways in which we contact
you).
Respond to your employment inquiries and applications – To evaluate your                     No                   Implicit
qualifications and complete required background and reference checks when you
apply for an open position at GFT Markets.
All financial companies need to share customers' personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list
the ways in which GFT Markets may share your personal information. Such activities may require transferring your personal
information across borders to service providers and affiliates in other countries.
                                                                                                            PRIVACY POLICY (UK English): 02/14/2014
                                                                                                                                      Revision: 002
                                                                                                                                         Page 1 of 3

Reasons we may share your personal information                                                 Can you limit       Consent
                                                                                               this sharing?
For our everyday business purposes – Such as to process your transactions,                     No                  Implicit
maintain your account(s), comply with legal obligations, or request information from
credit bureaus. This would include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our
website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to
keep this information confidential.
For our marketing purposes – With service providers that we use to offer our                   Yes                 Explicit
products and services to you (please see below to limit the ways in which we contact
you)
For our affiliates' everyday business purposes – Such as to process your                       No                  Implicit
transactions, maintain your account(s), comply with legal obligations, or request
information from credit bureaus.
For our affiliates to market to you                                                            Yes                 Explicit
To limit our usage or sharing of your personal information, please use the links found at the foot of the emails that you receive
from us or contact GFT Markets to change your preferences.
Please note:
You may continue to receive marketing information in regular account mailings and statements. You may also be contacted to
service your account or participate in surveys. If you have an assigned client manager or team, they may continue to contact you to
assist you in managing your portfolio or account relationship.
What happens when I limit sharing or usage for an account that I hold jointly with someone else?
Your preferences for sharing and usage of your personal information will apply individually unless you tell us otherwise. Any account
holder may express a privacy preference on behalf of the other joint account holders.
How do I access and update my personal information?
In order to provide high quality customer service, it is essential for you to provide GFT Markets with accurate and complete personal
information and inform us of any changes in a timely manner. We will periodically ask you to review and update your personal
information, but you may request access to and/or update your personal information at any time by contacting GFT Markets.
Please note:
If GFT Markets is unable to verify the accuracy of the information, GFT Markets may be unable to make such updates/changes to
your personal information as requested by you.
How long does GFT Markets keep my personal information?
GFT Markets only keeps your personal information on file for as long as it is required to provide you with products and services and
to meet legal requirements. When GFT Markets no longer needs your personal information, it is either securely destroyed or made
anonymous.
What does GFT Markets do to protect my personal information?
GFT Markets has implemented multiple physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards in compliance with applicable laws and
regulations to guard your personal information from unauthorized access, alteration, or premature destruction.
For more information, visit the Security section of our website.
Does GFT Markets use cookies or other tracking technology?
Various tools and techniques are used to gather and analyze website visits and sessions. One of the ways that we gather
information about visits is through cookies. Cookies are electronic files recorded by your browser that retain information about your
website visits on your computer.
We use cookies to record information on visits and use of our websites; this is so we can administer and improve our websites. We
do not use cookies to store or transmit any personal information without your explicit consent. Temporary "session" cookies are also
used to facilitate your navigation within our site during their visit. Session cookies are deleted once you close your Internet browser.
We may also use "persistent" cookies that are retained on your computer after your visit ends, so we can identify your preferences
and enhance your next visit to our websites.
                                                                                                             PRIVACY POLICY (UK English): 02/14/2014
                                                                                                                                       Revision: 002
                                                                                                                                          Page 2 of 3

In addition, cookies help us manage and monitor internet traffic from third-party websites to ours as well as which areas of our
websites are used most often and for how long. We may provide this type of aggregate information to non-affiliated application
service providers that compile statistical or other information for us. This feedback and analysis allows us to continually update our
websites.
You can block cookies by changing the settings on your internet browser or through the use of software programs specifically
designed to block cookies. You should be aware that by blocking cookies or using certain security software settings that these
actions may prevent you from logging onto your accounts or limit your online activities.
Does this policy apply to third party websites?
We may partner with reputable third party companies that help provide additional products and services or information to you online.
These third parties are always subject to a detailed evaluation process to review their relevant business practices however they may
have different online disclosures, including security and privacy practices, than GFT Markets. Be sure to review their respective
disclosures and policies.
What happens if GFT Markets changes their privacy policy?
We will review our Privacy Policy from time to time to ensure it is compliant with relevant laws and takes account of any changes to
our operations and practices. If it is necessary to make changes to our Privacy Policy, we will update this document with the
changes and new effective date. A notification may also be sent to you based on regional laws and regulations.
GFT Markets is a trading name of GAIN Capital – FOREX.com UK Limited and is authorised and regulated by the Financial Conduct
Authority. FCA No. 190864.
                                                                                                            PRIVACY POLICY (UK English): 02/14/2014
                                                                                                                                      Revision: 002
                                                                                                                                         Page 3 of 3
